<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="10" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.26" end="00:00:05.32">Hi, my name is Alice Begley, and I&apos;m a financial aid counselor here at DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:05.32" end="00:00:09.06">In order to get started with the financial aid process, the first thing you need</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:09.06" end="00:00:13.77">to do is complete the Free Application for Federal Student Aid.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:13.77" end="00:00:15.65">It&apos;s also known as the FAFSA.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:15.65" end="00:00:23.36">Go to www.fafsa.ed.gov to complete this process.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:23.36" end="00:00:29.00">When you complete your FAFSA, you will need you tax information from the current year.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:29.00" end="00:00:37.05">So if we&apos;re filing the 2010-2011 FAFSA, you would need your taxes from 2009.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:37.05" end="00:00:41.87">When this process is completed we will get the information from the Federal government,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:41.87" end="00:00:45.83">which will give us an EFC-an Estimated Family Contribution.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:45.83" end="00:00:53.40">This is what we use in order to package you with scholarships or grants.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:53.40" end="00:01:00.77">You will also need to go to www.studentloans.gov to complete your Master Promissory Note</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:00.77" end="00:01:04.27">and entrance counseling for your student loan.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:04.27" end="00:01:08.15">We are going with direct loans now, so we go directly to the Dept.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:08.15" end="00:01:09.16">of Education.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:09.16" end="00:01:14.11">In the ACCESS program, it is divided into trimesters.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:14.11" end="00:01:19.88">We have the Fall Trimester, the Spring Trimester, and the Summer Trimester.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:19.88" end="00:01:26.37">You must be enrolled in at least six credits in each trimester to receive financial aid.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:26.37" end="00:01:31.01">In order to receive the Pennsylvania State Grant, you need to be enrolled</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:31.01" end="00:01:34.06">in every session in every trimester.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:34.06" end="00:01:39.34">Your FAFSA would need to be filed by May 1st of each year in order</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:39.34" end="00:01:43.36">to be considered for the state grant.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:43.36" end="00:01:49.02">The way we figure your financial aid, is we create a budget for you.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:49.02" end="00:01:56.37">You take your tuition, with books, and living expenses-that would be your budget.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:56.37" end="00:02:01.11">Then we subtract your Estimated Family Contribution to come up with your need.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:01.11" end="00:02:03.87">Then your loans are based on your need.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:03.87" end="00:02:07.25">If you&apos;re eligible for a Pell Grant, that will be deducted</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:07.25" end="00:02:10.19">from your need, along with your state grant.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:10.19" end="00:02:16.83">If you have any need left, that would make your loan go into the subsidized category.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:16.83" end="00:02:19.99">If you don&apos;t have need, it will go into unsubsidized.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:19.99" end="00:02:26.59">As an independent student, you would be eligible for both subsidized and unsubsidized loans.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:26.59" end="00:02:32.83">If you drop any classes in your trimester-six credits is part time,</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:32.83" end="00:02:36.67">12 credits is full time-if you want to drop any</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:36.67" end="00:02:41.80">of your classes it could impact your financial aid.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:41.80" end="00:02:44.89">So you should really contact your advisor</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:44.89" end="00:02:49.51">or the financial aid office before you drop a class to see how this would impact.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:49.51" end="00:02:53.52">If you have any additional questions, you can call our office</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:53.52" end="00:03:02.28">at 610-282-1100 extensions 1287 or 1449.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:02.28" end="00:03:11.36">You can contact us through e-mail at finaid@desales.edu.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:11.36" end="00:03:12.27">And, good luck!</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>

</tt>
