<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="10" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.30" end="00:00:01.70">Hello and welcome veteran.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:01.70" end="00:00:05.56">My name is Judy Schwartz, and I&apos;m the Veteran&apos;s Affairs certifying official</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:05.56" end="00:00:07.73">for DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:07.73" end="00:00:13.51">We proudly welcome all military personal whether you have served or are currently serving.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:13.51" end="00:00:18.17">We have on-campus courses and also online courses.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:18.17" end="00:00:21.39">We do know that the demands of your personal life, families,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:21.39" end="00:00:24.43">careers and your military services and are here</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:24.43" end="00:00:29.03">to provide the most flexibility while earning your degree.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:29.03" end="00:00:34.81">We have more than doubled our enrolment of veteran students and hope to continue to grow.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:34.81" end="00:00:41.09">One of the newest and exciting GI Bills is the post 9/11 bill, also known as Chapter 33.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:41.09" end="00:00:45.51">It&apos;s a wonderful benefit for all veterans as well as all of the other GI benefits.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:45.51" end="00:00:48.63">I have a true interest in our military,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:48.63" end="00:00:53.63">my son Andrew is in the National Guard, the 56th Striker Brigade.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:53.63" end="00:00:56.66">And he was deployed last year to Iraq.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:56.66" end="00:00:59.17">I think that because of this I can be of service</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:59.17" end="00:01:03.55">to our military students and be sensitive to their needs.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:03.55" end="00:01:07.41">It is with great honor I can help them with their VA benefits.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:07.41" end="00:01:11.90">You can learn more about your education benefits and application process</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:11.90" end="00:01:18.92">by visiting our website, www.desales.edu/military.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:18.92" end="00:01:22.97">I work in the Registrars&apos; Office which is located in Dooling Hall and would be more</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:22.97" end="00:01:28.43">than happy to answer any questions and help with the process of your military benefits.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:28.43" end="00:01:30.33">Once again, welcome Veterans.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>

</tt>
