<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="13" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.62" end="00:00:07.52">The tools that I use to make sure that I&apos;m connected and current with activities</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:07.52" end="00:00:11.87">and changes in classes or Angel or WebAdvisor, web email.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:11.87" end="00:00:18.22">My Web email is my primary communication tool with the staff and the different departments</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:18.22" end="00:00:21.75">because it&apos;s an integrated system, but we&apos;re on different levels</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:21.75" end="00:00:24.04">of schedule and timings and such.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:24.04" end="00:00:27.14">And I think this is a great tool because we&apos;re busy.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:27.14" end="00:00:28.18">We&apos;re very busy.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:28.18" end="00:00:32.02">I don&apos;t always have the time to call an instructor or call the department.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:32.02" end="00:00:36.15">But if I drop an email most people if you&apos;re like me you, have your computer on</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:36.15" end="00:00:38.21">and it pops right up and you get an instant message.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:38.21" end="00:00:42.17">So, I think it&apos;s facilitate communication in an easier manner.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:42.17" end="00:00:46.23">So I use WebAdivisor if I want to know what&apos;s going on with my financial aid,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:46.23" end="00:00:49.52">if I want to know what&apos;s going on with my classes.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:49.52" end="00:00:52.72">If I sign up for a class or request a class, it&apos;s the quickest way is for me to find</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:52.72" end="00:00:57.56">out whether that class is open or they&apos;re&apos; not scheduling that class.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:57.56" end="00:01:01.21">ANGEL is the way I track my grades.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:01.21" end="00:01:05.61">I submit all my online homework and assignments that way.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:05.61" end="00:01:09.70">It is also one of the tools that I use the tools that I use to communicate specifically</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:09.70" end="00:01:12.93">with my instructors and the class members.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:12.93" end="00:01:15.84">I find it is very helpful because you don&apos;t&apos; have to make appointments,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:15.84" end="00:01:17.92">and you can get an instantaneous response.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:17.92" end="00:01:21.12">You can make your request know when you&apos;re thinking of something</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:21.12" end="00:01:22.72">or sharing an idea with your classmates.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:22.72" end="00:01:26.86">So i think WebAdvisor, ANGEL, and Webmail--</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:26.86" end="00:01:31.91">they&apos;re really integral to the success of the student at DeSales University</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>


</tt>
