<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="13" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.32" end="00:00:02.09">Welcome to DeSales!</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:02.09" end="00:00:07.62">I am Tonya Amankwatia, director of distance education and instructional technology.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:07.62" end="00:00:11.19">In the next few minutes, I will explain how you gain access</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:11.19" end="00:00:16.33">to important academic technology tools and resources.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:16.33" end="00:00:20.20">We hope it&apos;s apparent that DSU strives to provide a variety</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:20.20" end="00:00:23.61">of quality resources for teaching and learning.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:23.61" end="00:00:29.20">This overview, however, focuses on a few key tools and their functions.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:29.20" end="00:00:35.04">Web Advisor is a database that gives students online access to a wealth of vital information</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:35.04" end="00:00:40.09">such as course schedules, grades, transcripts, graduation,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:40.09" end="00:00:42.89">financial aid and payment information.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:42.89" end="00:00:46.88">It&apos;s also the place where you update your personal information found</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:46.88" end="00:00:49.63">in the Student Profile.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:49.63" end="00:00:56.21">The student profile area of WebAdvisor also stores your library bar code needed</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:56.21" end="00:01:03.48">for accessing Trexler library resources online as well as your initial password needed</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:03.48" end="00:01:07.50">for logging in to our learning management system for the first time.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:07.50" end="00:01:13.56">Make sure you sign up for our Campus alert system through WebAdvisor.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:13.56" end="00:01:20.82">This way you have campus closures and emergency messages sent to your cell phone.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:20.82" end="00:01:25.75">Another key tool is DSU email powered by Google.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:25.75" end="00:01:30.54">With your DSU Gmail account, you have access to a wealth of Google Apps!</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:30.54" end="00:01:34.03">Be sure to check email regularly for DSU news.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:34.03" end="00:01:44.58">In cyberspace, online and hybrid classes occur in a Learning Management System or LMS.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:44.58" end="00:01:51.34">Some popular LMS examples are ANGEL, Blackboard, Moodle, and Desire2Learn.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:51.34" end="00:02:01.33">Within the LMS, students find online tutoring resources, an orientation to online learning,</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:01.33" end="00:02:05.36">library links, and our Web collaboration tools.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:05.36" end="00:02:11.00">Enrollment in the LMS is automatic through WebAdvisor.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:11.00" end="00:02:18.84">At this point you might be thinking, &quot;Dr. A this all sounds great, so when do I get access?&quot;</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:18.84" end="00:02:27.33">You will be notified of their Web Advisor, email, and LMS account information</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:27.33" end="00:02:30.97">after you are admitted to the University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:30.97" end="00:02:36.63">All technology problems or account questions should be directed to the DSU Help Desk</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:36.63" end="00:02:53.71">at helpdesk@desles.edu or 610.282.1100 x4357.My final piece</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:53.71" end="00:03:04.86">of advice is to use good security measures.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:04.86" end="00:03:12.24">Be diligent about changing your password when prompted and never share your password</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:12.24" end="00:03:22.07">with anyone, avoid suspicious files and pirated media file downloads, and never send credit card</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:22.07" end="00:03:29.96">or social security data to anyone via email.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>

</tt>
