<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="13" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.22" end="00:00:04.74">The tools that were provided from the technological standpoint--</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:04.74" end="00:00:08.72">on ANGEL and Blackboard and Elluminate session-- helped me.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:08.72" end="00:00:11.58">They just enhanced my experience in the classroom.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:11.58" end="00:00:15.97">At my convenience any time of night or day, if I couldn&apos;t sleep, if it was early</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:15.97" end="00:00:20.75">and the house was quiet, I could jump on, check my homework for the week, check my last grade</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:20.75" end="00:00:25.45">on my test, just have messages for the professor or other classmates.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:25.45" end="00:00:31.76">It was just extremely accessible at my convenience, and that overall helped</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:31.76" end="00:00:35.12">to enhance my experience with the program.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:35.12" end="00:00:36.76">WebAdvisor was fantastic.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:36.76" end="00:00:39.38">I actually underutilized it in the beginning.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:39.38" end="00:00:44.01">Once I found out all it had to offer, I was constantly checking on a date,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:44.01" end="00:00:48.61">maybe checking my bill and the financial office, or checking my average.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:48.61" end="00:00:52.45">Of course after the exams, I would check it a few times a day to see</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:52.45" end="00:00:54.08">where my final grade had come in.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:54.08" end="00:00:57.05">I found the student email to be extremely helpful.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:57.05" end="00:01:01.41">The instructors were accessible, they always got back within a couple of hours.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:01.41" end="00:01:05.51">I worked on many, many group projects, so the email came in handy.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:05.51" end="00:01:08.30">I could correspond with just the people in my group,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:08.30" end="00:01:11.25">or if I had a question for the class, I could ask them.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:11.25" end="00:01:16.12">And if somebody was leaving one of our courses, going into another , often it was not uncommon</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:16.12" end="00:01:19.44">to get an email from them asking, &quot;Does anybody have this book.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:19.44" end="00:01:20.42">I&apos;d like to buy it.&quot;</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:20.42" end="00:01:22.68">So it really helped in all different ways.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>


</tt>
