<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="10" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
 
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.06" end="00:00:04.11">Hi I&apos;m Marisa McFadden and I&apos;m a writing instructor here at DeSales University</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:04.11" end="00:00:06.75">for the access program and I&apos;m going to talk to you today</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:06.75" end="00:00:10.33">about plagiarism and what it is specifically.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:10.33" end="00:00:15.63">Plagiarism is when you claim someone else&apos;s ideas as your own and it&apos;s a big problem</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:15.63" end="00:00:21.00">across college campuses throughout the country because we all have access to the Internet,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:21.00" end="00:00:24.32">the television and lots of material at college libraries.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:24.32" end="00:00:28.71">And so when we want to get an answer to a question, it&apos;s right there at our finger tips.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:28.71" end="00:00:33.53">The issue arises when we don&apos;t give credit to the source that we got the answer from.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:33.53" end="00:00:38.35">So when we find out material or we find ideas interesting and we share them with others,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:38.35" end="00:00:43.56">it&apos;s important that we give credit to the source material or the source of those ideas.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:43.56" end="00:00:47.51">So if I read a New York Times article and I want to share the contents of that article</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:47.51" end="00:00:51.57">with a friend of mine, it would be unintentionally plagiarizing if I failed</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:51.57" end="00:00:55.24">to mention or forgot to mention where the article came from.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:55.24" end="00:00:58.28">And for me to avoid plagiarism I would just say &quot;Oh and by the way,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:58.28" end="00:01:00.22">I read that in the New York Times.&quot;</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:00.22" end="00:01:02.65">In an academic setting you&apos;d do it in a more formal way</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:02.65" end="00:01:05.78">by following a style guide like MLA or APA .</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:05.78" end="00:01:10.95">You&apos;ll learn about those in your EN103 and EN104 classes.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:10.95" end="00:01:15.41">There are resources around the campus that can help you avoid plagiarism--</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:15.41" end="00:01:21.22">resources such as all the APA and MLA workshops that are offered through the Trexler library.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:21.22" end="00:01:24.82">Check the schedule for the library because they are offered a few times a month</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:24.82" end="00:01:27.62">and they&apos;re really informative and they&apos;re really helpful.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:27.62" end="00:01:31.09">You also have the librarians there to help you and they&apos;re willing to talk to you</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:31.09" end="00:01:33.38">by phone, by email and face to face.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:33.38" end="00:01:35.64">Your professors are also a good resource for you</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:35.64" end="00:01:38.28">if you have any questions about what plagiarism is.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:38.28" end="00:01:44.04">They understand MLA, APA and Chicago Format very well and can help you avoid plagiarism</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:44.04" end="00:01:47.20">by teaching you a little bit more about each of those formats.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:47.20" end="00:01:51.69">There&apos;s plenty of resources for you to tap into for avoiding plagiarism here at DeSales,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:51.69" end="00:01:56.35">so just log onto ANGEL , log onto the DeSales website, or just ask one of your professors</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:56.35" end="00:02:00.16">or a librarian a little bit more about plagiarism.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:00.16" end="00:02:01.33">Thank you for watching.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>

</tt>
