<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="12" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.85" end="00:00:05.58">Juggling school, family, and career is a challenging, but worthwhile task.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:05.58" end="00:00:07.88">However, it doesn&apos;t have to be a chore.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:07.88" end="00:00:11.97">While appearing simplistic, there are some very basic, commonsense approaches</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:11.97" end="00:00:14.65">to maintaining a healthy balance.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:15.79" end="00:00:18.95">It&apos;s important to take the time to be good to yourself.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:18.95" end="00:00:24.68">Remember the basics things required for good health...diet, sleep, and exercise.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:24.68" end="00:00:28.50">While being necessary for your overall wellbeing, they help to keep you</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:28.50" end="00:00:32.00">at the top of your game academically.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:32.00" end="00:00:34.99">Look around you, particularly where you study.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:34.99" end="00:00:39.15">It&apos;s much easier, and more pleasant, to study where you&apos;re comfortable.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:39.15" end="00:00:42.45">For some that might be in at a desk in a well-lit room.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:42.45" end="00:00:46.74">For others it might be stretched out on the living room floor.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:46.74" end="00:00:49.25">Plan when and how you&apos;re going to study.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:49.25" end="00:00:50.70">Will it be after dinner?</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:50.70" end="00:00:52.56">After the children are in bed?</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:52.56" end="00:00:54.10">During a lunch break?</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:54.10" end="00:00:58.81">Planning will help you to not study any longer than is necessary.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:58.81" end="00:01:06.46">Acknowledge you have another life-- family, career, hobbies-- things of importance to you.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:06.46" end="00:01:10.77">Come to terms with the realization you can&apos;t always do it all.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:10.77" end="00:01:13.04">Learn what&apos;s important when.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:13.04" end="00:01:15.76">You may be able to delegate some responsibilities</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:15.76" end="00:01:17.82">when you find yourself too busy.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:17.82" end="00:01:19.85">This does not admit defeat.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:19.85" end="00:01:23.12">It&apos;s just an admission that you&apos;re human and like all of use you need</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:23.12" end="00:01:26.12">to make adjustments from time to time.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:26.12" end="00:01:29.42">Along the way, take time to recognize your achievements,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:29.42" end="00:01:34.72">whether that be completing an important task at work on time, acing a biology final,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:34.72" end="00:01:38.45">or simply remembering to take out the garbage without being reminded.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:38.45" end="00:01:42.57">You may find yourself a bit overwhelmed upon returning to school</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:42.57" end="00:01:44.83">or going to school for the first time.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:44.83" end="00:01:48.47">Learning how to manage your time will help here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:48.47" end="00:01:52.38">Just some basics: keep a calendar, write things down.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:52.38" end="00:01:54.08">You&apos;re going to be busy.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:54.08" end="00:01:58.28">Don&apos;t rely on keeping it all in your head while trying to get other stuff in there,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:58.28" end="00:02:03.27">like mathematical formulas, management strategies, rules for writing.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:03.27" end="00:02:05.23">Try to establish a routine.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:05.23" end="00:02:07.20">But, don&apos;t be unrealistic.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:07.20" end="00:02:12.91">Reading or studying for six hours on a Saturday so Sunday is free may sound like a good plan.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:12.91" end="00:02:16.14">It&apos;s not effective in practice for several reasons.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:16.14" end="00:02:20.78">While getting into a routine is good, take time to reflect on how that routine,</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:20.78" end="00:02:24.82">how your time management, is working or not.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:24.82" end="00:02:26.84">Don&apos;t be afraid to make adjustments along way.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>


</tt>

