<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="12" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
 
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.31" end="00:00:02.24">Hi. My name&apos;s John Barkanic.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:02.24" end="00:00:04.74">I&apos;ve been with DeSales University in the ACCESS Program,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:04.74" end="00:00:07.71">Mathematics Department, for over 20 years now.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:07.71" end="00:00:11.86">Probably half the students who come into the math classes are stressed out.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:11.86" end="00:00:12.78">They have math anxiety.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:12.78" end="00:00:16.05">They have not exercised their math skills.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:16.05" end="00:00:20.71">The other half are pretty comfortable with mathematics, either from other courses</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:20.71" end="00:00:26.63">that they&apos;ve had, or because they&apos;ve done well in school-in other math courses in school,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:26.63" end="00:00:30.65">high school, or they have a feel for mathematics.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:30.65" end="00:00:33.59">For the half that is not comfortable or is stress out,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:33.59" end="00:00:37.94">there are couple of things that are useful.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:37.94" end="00:00:40.11">One is to not overload.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:40.11" end="00:00:45.50">Some people try to take double classes.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:45.50" end="00:00:49.85">My advice is don&apos;t try to take a math class coupled with some other course.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:49.85" end="00:00:55.73">There&apos;s enough work already in the math course to keep you busy the full eight weeks.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:55.73" end="00:00:59.14">The folks that do double up on classes,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:59.14" end="00:01:01.64">really don&apos;t get what they need to get out of the math class.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:01.64" end="00:01:06.71">Even if they pass it successfully, they&apos;re not really getting the education</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:06.71" end="00:01:08.57">from the course that they should be getting.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:08.57" end="00:01:15.36">That&apos;s one aspect of it.The second thing to deal with stress and anxiety is like anything else.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:15.36" end="00:01:19.41">If you don&apos;t know something you stress out about it.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:19.41" end="00:01:21.69">Most people who take the test, after the test,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:21.69" end="00:01:25.98">they look at the problem and say, &quot;This is so easy!</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:25.98" end="00:01:29.30">I see how to do it and it&apos;s so easy.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:29.30" end="00:01:31.78">Why couldn&apos;t I see it in the class?&quot;</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:31.78" end="00:01:37.23">Well, that awareness of how a problem comes together and why it&apos;s obvious now</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:37.23" end="00:01:40.58">that you know how to do it comes with practice.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:40.58" end="00:01:45.87">So you have to find a way to make the time to do problems.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:45.87" end="00:01:49.79">All the talk in the world isn&apos;t going to make you an expert in mathematics.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:49.79" end="00:01:54.31">Sitting through all the lectures in the world isn&apos;t going to make you skilled in mathematics.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:54.31" end="00:02:00.96">Until you take pencil to paper and start solving math problems, you&apos;re not going to be able</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:00.96" end="00:02:02.69">to take tests and do well on tests.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:02.69" end="00:02:07.21">And that&apos;s what this is about-- being able to test well,</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:07.21" end="00:02:09.62">understand the material and test well.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:09.62" end="00:02:13.70">You have to put pencil to paper, you have to solve problems, and that takes time.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:13.70" end="00:02:17.46">Just make time to practice.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:17.46" end="00:02:19.75">Find the time to practice the material.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>


</tt>



