<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  
<head>
   
<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="10" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  
</head>
  
<body>
   
<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    
<p begin="00:00:03.04" end="00:00:08.20">The biggest advice is to be just to take that first class.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:08.20" end="00:00:13.58">That first class is a big hurdle for a lto of people, especially for non-traditional students</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:13.58" end="00:00:19.29">that haven&apos;t been in school for awhile but you have to remember that you&apos;re not in it alone.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:19.29" end="00:00:23.00">You&apos;re going to meet a lot of great people from diverse backgrounds.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:23.00" end="00:00:25.64">But they&apos;re all there for the same reason-they want to learn.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:25.64" end="00:00:27.64">They want to finish something that they started.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:27.64" end="00:00:32.12">And you will get the support here that you&apos;re going to need.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:32.12" end="00:00:33.04">And don&apos;t be afraid.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:33.04" end="00:00:37.44">Just jump in with both feet and take a class and I think you&apos;ll be happy that you did.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:37.44" end="00:00:40.75">Jump in with both feet and take a class and I think you&apos;ll be happy that you did.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:40.75" end="00:00:47.17">The majority of instructors have gone to school part time nights in order to get where they are.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:47.17" end="00:00:52.41">So they understand that the students are not only going</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:52.41" end="00:00:53.82">to school but they&apos;re working full time.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:53.82" end="00:00:54.64">They have families.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:54.64" end="00:00:57.16">They have lives outside of that.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:57.16" end="00:00:58.55">I&apos;ve never had any issues.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:58.55" end="00:01:02.37">I&apos;ve always spoken to my instructors beforehand if I needed any vacation.</p>

<p begin="00:01:02.37" end="00:01:04.77">It will be over faster than you think.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:04.77" end="00:01:06.50">I don&apos;t know where the last 3 years went.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:06.50" end="00:01:07.25">It was pretty quick.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:07.25" end="00:01:10.00">It seems like it&apos;s going to take forever to finish your degree,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:10.00" end="00:01:14.25">but the longer you stall off getting started, the longer it is before you get finished.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:14.25" end="00:01:19.25">But don&apos;t be afraid some classes that you might not necessarily think are that important</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:19.25" end="00:01:23.25">to you -- so the ones that are required for some of the Gen Ed credits.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:23.25" end="00:01:25.25">Western Civ</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:25.25" end="00:01:27.15">was one of the ones that I had to have.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:27.15" end="00:01:31.53">And after I took the first one I couldn&apos;t wait to take the second one.</p>  

</div>

</body>

</tt>
