<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 <tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  
<head>
   
<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="13" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  
</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.43" end="00:00:04.05">Hi my name is Debbie Boros the Dean of Lifelong Learning.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:04.05" end="00:00:07.22">Congratulations on your decision to return to school,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:07.22" end="00:00:12.07">welcome to the access program and DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:12.07" end="00:00:17.89">Many of you have had a 5, 10 or 15 year hiatus from going back to school.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:17.89" end="00:00:23.03">As a new student you&apos;re full of enthusiasm and maybe just a little anxiety</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:23.03" end="00:00:28.91">and hesitation even before you step in to the virtual or face to face classroom.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:28.91" end="00:00:35.43">So we wanted to create a special orientation experience tailored to meet your diverse needs.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:35.43" end="00:00:40.08">We value and respect your life experiences so it is important</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:40.08" end="00:00:45.51">that this orientation is relevant to adult learners.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:45.51" end="00:00:52.56">The goal of the orientation is not to burden you with on policies and procedures</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:52.56" end="00:00:57.82">that will push you to the threshold of information overload but to provide you</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:57.82" end="00:01:01.36">with strategies for academic success.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:01.36" end="00:01:04.43">For example: how is your life going to change?</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:04.43" end="00:01:08.92">Where will you go if you need some resources or services?</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:08.92" end="00:01:12.58">How are you going to learn to use the technology?</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:12.58" end="00:01:18.16">The orientation will cover all of these answers and more including registration,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:18.16" end="00:01:25.35">how to write a research paper and yes, even how to get through that much dreaded math course</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:25.35" end="00:01:31.36">and you will be able to interact with one another, with staff and with future professors.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:31.36" end="00:01:36.03">You will get to meet some of our current students who will talk about their experiences</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:36.03" end="00:01:41.19">and challenges in the access program and they will give you some good tips on how</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:41.19" end="00:01:46.84">to juggle family, work, community commitments and school.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:46.84" end="00:01:53.09">So please take your time as you go through the orientation, we can go in and out and use it</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:53.09" end="00:01:59.46">as a future reference but please take the time to complete the orientation.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:59.46" end="00:02:05.20">It&apos;s important to understand the program so that you can focus on your studies instead</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:05.20" end="00:02:10.18">of worrying about deadlines or misinterpreted policies.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:10.18" end="00:02:16.02">Most importantly, get to know your advisor they understand the challenges of returning to school</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:16.02" end="00:02:22.01">as an adult learner, so take advantage of their knowledge, guidance and support.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:22.01" end="00:02:26.86">I really enjoy meeting and talking with students and finding out how they are doing</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:26.86" end="00:02:31.45">in the program so I hope you&apos;ll take a few minutes to stop in and say hello to me.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:31.45" end="00:02:33.64">I look forward to meeting you.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:33.64" end="00:02:38.08">I wish you much success in your academic endeavors.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:38.08" end="00:02:42.55">Thank you again for putting your education in the hands of access.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:42.55" end="00:02:43.26">Please take care.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>


</tt>
