<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  
<head>
   
<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="13" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  
</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.38" end="00:00:02.49">Welcome to our ACCESS online program.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:02.49" end="00:00:06.44">My name is Father Tom Dailey and I direct the Salesian Center for Faith</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:06.44" end="00:00:08.89">and Culture here at DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:08.89" end="00:00:12.68">Salesian is one of those words that we use that refers to Saint Francis DeSales</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:12.68" end="00:00:15.49">who is the patron of the university.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:15.49" end="00:00:19.81">I&apos;ve been asked to chat with you briefly about the mission of the university and some</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:19.81" end="00:00:26.30">of the common core courses that everyone here at DeSales takes even in the online program.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:26.30" end="00:00:31.88">In thinking about this, I was laughing to myself that we are doing here</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:31.88" end="00:00:34.81">in the 21st century a new version</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:34.81" end="00:00:39.27">of what Francis DeSales did some 400 years ago in France.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:39.27" end="00:00:43.87">At the time the new technology in those days was the printing press,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:43.87" end="00:00:48.46">and Saint Francis De Sales is known for having made use of the printing press</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:48.46" end="00:00:54.00">to spread the message about Catholicism to people all around Switzerland.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:54.00" end="00:01:00.36">It was precisely that new technology that helped him to get people&apos;s attention and to get them</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:00.36" end="00:01:05.98">to talk about some of the more important things they were considering in life.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:05.98" end="00:01:07.43">In essence that&apos;s what we&apos;re doing here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:07.43" end="00:01:13.52">As a university as a whole, we seek in all that we teach to talk</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:13.52" end="00:01:16.34">about the important things, to talk about truth.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:16.34" end="00:01:20.63">And as you know, truth comes in many forms.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:20.63" end="00:01:28.07">In the sense that we&apos;re going to teach you courses that will give you the truth</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:28.07" end="00:01:32.52">in whatever subject matter you&apos;re studying, whatever it is that you&apos;re majoring in--</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:32.52" end="00:01:35.95">the skills in business, the techniques in science--</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:35.95" end="00:01:38.32">or whatever it is that you&apos;re studying.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:38.32" end="00:01:43.08">But there are also truths of a different nature that go beyond that sort</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:43.08" end="00:01:47.34">of scientific and technical skill level.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:47.34" end="00:01:51.09">So for instance, the truth about beauty in life--</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:51.09" end="00:01:58.46">we have a stellar performing and fine arts here on campus and we celebrate that truth</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:58.46" end="00:02:02.32">that is beauty a truth that every human being knows</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.32" end="00:02:05.40">when you see a really good show or dance performance.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:05.40" end="00:02:09.93">We talk about truth in terms of philosophy or theology.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:09.93" end="00:02:14.54">These all the kinds of courses that everyone at the university is going to have to take as part</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:14.54" end="00:02:21.17">of our general education core curriculum because we believe there is a core of knowledge</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:21.17" end="00:02:25.48">that affects every human being, no matter what it is you&apos;re studying,</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:25.48" end="00:02:29.46">because it goes to the heart of what it means to be a human being.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:29.46" end="00:02:36.24">So even online, you&apos;ll be asked to think about deep questions to ponder the mysteries of life</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:36.24" end="00:02:41.71">to come up with some answers for yourselves because whatever knowledge it is</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:41.71" end="00:02:48.60">that you&apos;re going to take form these online courses it&apos;s really that knowledge not simply</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:48.60" end="00:02:53.29">about the content but knowledge about yourself that&apos;s important.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:53.29" end="00:02:58.85">So even as you learn to master this new technology of online courses,</p>
   
<p begin="00:02:58.85" end="00:03:02.97">remember that learning isn&apos;t just about learning stuff,</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:02.97" end="00:03:07.68">or learning new technologies or new gadgets.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:07.68" end="00:03:11.60">It&apos;s really untimely learning about ourselves.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:11.60" end="00:03:18.38">This is primarily the mission of the university it is a profound teaching of Francis DeSales</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:18.38" end="00:03:27.40">from 400 years ago who taught that, among other things his, one of his more famous sayings is</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:27.40" end="00:03:30.67">that we should be who we are and be that perfectly well.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:30.67" end="00:03:36.04">What he meant by that is that we kind of waste our time and energy if we&apos;re trying</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:36.04" end="00:03:39.50">to be someone else if we&apos;re trying to be something that we&apos;re not.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:39.50" end="00:03:41.48">Because every single one of us, every single one</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:41.48" end="00:03:45.20">of you taking these courses, is gifted in a unique way.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:45.20" end="00:03:49.04">So be that, and become that, and learn more about that</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:49.04" end="00:03:53.37">and be who you are, and be that perfectly well.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:53.37" end="00:03:54.74">That&apos;s our mission.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:54.74" end="00:03:58.67">That&apos;s what grounds out educational philosophy.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:58.67" end="00:04:03.88">That&apos;s why you&apos;ll be taking a lot of courses that may be outside you&apos;re area of interest</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:03.88" end="00:04:07.25">or outside of your area of expertise.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:07.25" end="00:04:11.72">But they&apos;re courses that hopefully will make you expert in being human.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:11.72" end="00:04:15.49">So again, welcome to DeSales University and the online program-doing</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:15.49" end="00:04:21.62">in the 21st century the very same things that Francis DeSales did 400 years ago.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:21.62" end="00:04:27.79">Hopefully you will join with us in continuing that tradition of learning to be</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:27.79" end="00:04:30.28">who we are and to be that perfectly well.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>

</tt>
