<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   
<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="13" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  
</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:02.68" end="00:00:05.25">Well, DeSales was nice and convenient as far as location.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:05.25" end="00:00:08.62">I was working at L. L. Bean at the time and it was very close to work.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:08.62" end="00:00:13.88">The flexible schedule-- the ability to start and stop when I needed to, and really,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:13.88" end="00:00:18.13">the accelerated format of having 8-week courses and being able to get all my classes</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:18.13" end="00:00:21.01">in in a timely manner to get everything done was really a key</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:21.01" end="00:00:22.83">and important reason for coming here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:22.83" end="00:00:28.34">I did check various schools in the area and I felt that DeSales fit my lifestyle.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:28.34" end="00:00:37.26">I was able to choose the courses I wanted, when I wanted, and it wasn&apos;t a continuous team thing</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:37.26" end="00:00:38.76">that the other schools seemed to be.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:38.76" end="00:00:42.05">It was more a school that graded you on you.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:42.05" end="00:00:48.03">First of all, I&apos;m Catholic and I like the idea of going to a Catholic university.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:48.03" end="00:00:55.04">Plus the flexibility in the scheduling, the class sizes were excellent.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:55.04" end="00:00:56.24">It was just convenient.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:56.24" end="00:00:57.49">I live in the Lehigh Valley.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:57.49" end="00:00:59.80">It has an excellent reputation.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:59.80" end="00:01:04.79">I believe it&apos;s been over 30 years that the program&apos;s been in progress.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:04.79" end="00:01:11.83">That&apos;s really what drove me to make my decision to attend the program.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:11.83" end="00:01:16.25">What appealed to me most in what DeSales had to offer in ACCESS was the fast, 8-week.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:16.25" end="00:01:21.00">A lot of work but you got the credits in 8 weeks.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:21.00" end="00:01:23.00">So you are able to do it in a much shorter time.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:23.00" end="00:01:28.63">And being and adult in a busy world, it afforded me an instant gratification on those.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:28.63" end="00:01:32.62">I was no sooner able to get head deep into the course and it would be ending,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:32.62" end="00:01:34.91">and I&apos;d be moving on to something else.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:34.91" end="00:01:36.74">I did like the rapid pace.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:36.74" end="00:01:37.67">That appealed to me.</p>
   
</div>
  
</body>

</tt>
