<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="12" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:03.02" end="00:00:08.32">As a student, you need to be in charge of your education.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:08.32" end="00:00:12.96">That&apos;s probably one of the most important things that you can do in order</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:12.96" end="00:00:15.32">to be successful in college anywhere.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:15.32" end="00:00:19.45">You need to do your homework- not just in the classroom,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:19.45" end="00:00:22.02">but also before you&apos;re coming to see your advisor.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:22.02" end="00:00:25.20">My advisor really helps get me on track.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:25.20" end="00:00:33.56">When I started ACCESS, I knew I needed to go to school, and I had a million ideas of what it was</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:33.56" end="00:00:38.62">that I wanted to go to school for, and what I thought I wanted to do.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:38.62" end="00:00:44.07">My advisor was able to sit down with me and talk to me more and find out my interests,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:44.07" end="00:00:50.68">what I want to do with my life, what I was good at-all those things-help me figure</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:50.68" end="00:00:52.24">out the right track.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:52.24" end="00:00:56.84">When we picked out my first classes, she really tried to help me pick</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:56.84" end="00:01:02.96">out things she knew I would be comfortable with, because these were my first college courses.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:02.96" end="00:01:03.93">It was great.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:03.93" end="00:01:08.87">My first classes were a really great experience for me.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:08.87" end="00:01:12.36">I think I certainly had a million questions for her.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:12.36" end="00:01:19.37">I wanted to know everything, from, Where is the library exactly?, to &quot;How do I get my books?</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:19.37" end="00:01:24.56">I had every question in the world, and she was able to answer them.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:24.56" end="00:01:28.46">If she wasn&apos;t&apos; able to answer them, she found those answers for me.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:28.46" end="00:01:33.23">It was really great to know that she was trying to get to know me,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:33.23" end="00:01:37.24">and I was able to get all I needed to know from her.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>

</tt>
