<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="12" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.40" end="00:00:03.25">Hello. Welcome to DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:03.25" end="00:00:08.09">My name is Karen Tempinksi, and I am the Former Police Chief here at DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:08.09" end="00:00:13.04">On behalf the men and women of my staff, I would like to welcome you to DeSales.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:13.04" end="00:00:15.56">We are very happy to have you here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:15.56" end="00:00:19.44">We are very blessed to have a very low crime rate here at DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:19.44" end="00:00:22.99">We have officers on 24-hours, 7 days a week.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:22.99" end="00:00:29.37">You can contact any police officer by telephone, or in person at the Police Department</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:29.37" end="00:00:32.58">which is located at the Lawless Center.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:32.58" end="00:00:37.62">In addition to investigative reports, officers are also concerned</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:37.62" end="00:00:39.85">about your health and well being.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:39.85" end="00:00:45.85">We offer a variety of crime prevention services, such as self-defense classes.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:45.85" end="00:00:50.09">We offer personal property engraving, which means if you have a laptop,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:50.09" end="00:00:54.14">we will be happy to engrave a unique serial number onto that piece of property.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:54.14" end="00:00:57.08">In the event it is lost or stolen, that way,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:57.08" end="00:01:00.52">if that item is later found, we can return it to you.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:00.52" end="00:01:04.93">If you would like a ride across campus, you are unsure about walking,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:04.93" end="00:01:09.68">simply pick up the telephone and dial extension 1250 and an officer will be happy</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:09.68" end="00:01:14.49">to give you a ride from the classroom located in Dooling Hall to the library</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:14.49" end="00:01:17.43">or anywhere on campus free of charge.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:17.43" end="00:01:20.42">All students are required to have a parking permit.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:20.42" end="00:01:23.94">Getting a parking permit is very simple.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:23.94" end="00:01:26.90">Simply bring your vehicle owner&apos;s registration card</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:26.90" end="00:01:30.30">and your student identification card to the University Police Dept.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:30.30" end="00:01:32.19">located in Lawless.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:32.19" end="00:01:35.16">You will be asked to fill out a simple card.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:35.16" end="00:01:36.75">There is no parking permit fee.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:36.75" end="00:01:41.35">You will be given a parking permit and asked to place it on the right-rear bumper</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:41.35" end="00:01:46.91">of the vehicle, or you may also place it on the right rear window of the vehicle.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:46.91" end="00:01:51.36">All ACCESS and computer students are allowed to park in the following parking lots:</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:51.36" end="00:01:56.75">Dooling Hall, the University Center, Trexler Library,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:56.75" end="00:02:00.68">Billera Hall gymnasium, and the Labuda Center.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:00.68" end="00:02:03.87">Please do not park in any residence hall parking lots.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:03.87" end="00:02:08.29">If you park in a residence hall lot, you will be issued a parking ticket.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:08.29" end="00:02:10.50">If you receive a parking ticket, there are instructions</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:10.50" end="00:02:12.65">on the ticket on what you should do.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:12.65" end="00:02:16.14">Please do not ignore the ticket because the fines will double.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:16.14" end="00:02:20.44">If you have any questions, please call University Police at extension 1250,</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:20.44" end="00:02:22.62">and we&apos;ll be happy to answer any questions.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>

</tt>
