<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="12" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.09" end="00:00:04.67">Hi. I&apos;m Jeff Richter, Assistant Director of Auxiliary Services here at DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:04.67" end="00:00:08.82">Today I&apos;m going to give you a little look around the University Center here on campus.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:08.82" end="00:00:11.87">The first area I want to show you is our Conferences and Events Center.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:11.87" end="00:00:16.61">Here, every year we do thousands of camps, conferences and special events.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:16.61" end="00:00:19.75">On a day-to-day basis, we&apos;re serving our internal population,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:19.75" end="00:00:21.37">as well as external clients.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:21.37" end="00:00:25.17">We also have a full-service catering department to service the conference center.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:25.17" end="00:00:27.00">The next thing I want to show you is our dining hall.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:27.00" end="00:00:29.49">This is our main dining hall on campus.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:29.49" end="00:00:33.70">In this dining hall we can seat between 450 and 500 students</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:33.70" end="00:00:36.65">and during the school year, we feed three meals a day.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:36.65" end="00:00:42.75">We have a food court system with five different stations to serve our undergraduate population.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:42.75" end="00:00:45.30">Here in the University Center you&apos;ll find the Campus Store.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:45.30" end="00:00:48.56">The Campus Store is your one-stop shop for all your textbooks,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:48.56" end="00:00:51.66">school supplies and DeSales logo item needs.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:51.66" end="00:00:56.08">The Campus Store is usually open Monday through Friday and Saturday mornings.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:56.08" end="00:00:59.35">Also in the University Center, you&apos;ll find the University Card office</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:59.35" end="00:01:01.39">where you report to get your student ID.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:01.39" end="00:01:03.98">It&apos;s important that you get your student ID because you&apos;ll use it</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:03.98" end="00:01:06.07">for a multitude of things on campus.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>

</tt>
