<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="12" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.54" end="00:00:01.99">Hi, my name is Scott Coval.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:01.99" end="00:00:06.17">I&apos;m the Director of Athletics at DeSales University.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:06.17" end="00:00:10.08">I wanted to give you a brief overview of the Athletic Department</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:10.08" end="00:00:15.15">and opportunities you would have as an ACCESS student at DeSales.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:15.15" end="00:00:18.66">Billera Hall is located at the West end of campus.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:18.66" end="00:00:23.98">You will need a valid ID to enter Billera Hall.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:23.98" end="00:00:31.76">Once inside Billera Hall, you&apos;ll find a lot of opportunities to play and to work out.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:31.76" end="00:00:37.30">We have three recreation courts that you can use to play pick-up basketball or volleyball.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:37.30" end="00:00:43.12">We have newly renovated fitness center with Nautilus equipment, free weights, tread mills,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:43.12" end="00:00:49.88">elliptical machines, bicycles, rowers, anything you&apos;ll need to get a good workout.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:49.88" end="00:00:56.04">The hours in Billera Hall are Monday - Thursday from 7:00am to 11:00pm.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:56.04" end="00:00:59.35">Friday hours are 7:00am to 9:00pm.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:59.35" end="00:01:07.46">And on the weekends, we&apos;re open from 10:00-6:00 on Saturday and from 2:00 - 10:00 on Sunday.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:07.46" end="00:01:11.51">Along with Billera Hall, we have an all weather outdoor track.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:11.51" end="00:01:16.82">Again, with a valid ID, you can get on the track and use the track.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:16.82" end="00:01:27.69">We also have 6 very nice tennis courts that you can use as long as you have a valid student ID.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:27.69" end="00:01:34.83">We want to wish you the very best on your classes, and certainly, we would welcome you</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:34.83" end="00:01:39.24">to come down to Billera Hall and check us out and see what we have</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:39.24" end="00:01:41.82">to offer here in the Athletic Department.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>


</tt>
