<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

 
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1"  xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling">
  

<head>
   

<styling>
    
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="center" tts:color="#FFFFFF" tts:backgroundColor="#000000" tts:fontSize="12" tts:fontFamily="Verdana" tts:wrapOption="wrap"/>
   
</styling>
  

</head>
  

<body>
   

<div xml:lang="en" style="1">
    

<p begin="00:00:00.68" end="00:00:02.76">Hello, welcome to Trexler Library.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:02.76" end="00:00:06.50">My name is Debbie Malone, and I&apos;m the Library Director here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:06.50" end="00:00:09.43">And we&apos;re standing in the MacFadden Room in the second floor</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:09.43" end="00:00:14.21">of the library-our Salesian collection is housed here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:14.21" end="00:00:18.29">The library has about 150,000 bound volumes in the building.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:18.29" end="00:00:21.41">We have about 300 paper periodicals.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:21.41" end="00:00:25.02">But what will probably interest you the most is our online collection.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:25.02" end="00:00:29.42">We have about 40,000 electronic books that are available to you.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:29.42" end="00:00:35.56">We have over 25 databases that you have access to.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:35.56" end="00:00:43.59">We provide access to about 9,000 periodical titles or magazine articles that you can access</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:43.59" end="00:00:46.95">from your home, from your office, as well as in the library,</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:46.95" end="00:00:50.64">or in any of the computer labs on campus.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:50.64" end="00:00:57.52">I think the most important thing for you to know is that you need your DeSales ID</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:57.52" end="00:00:59.88">to access these online resources.</p>
    
<p begin="00:00:59.88" end="00:01:06.84">If you don&apos;t already have one, what you really need to do is look in your WebAdvisor profile,</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:06.84" end="00:01:11.21">and there&apos;s a library 14-digit barcode there, and that&apos;s what you&apos;ll need</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:11.21" end="00:01:18.00">to authenticate yourself into the system so you can have access to all this electronic material.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:18.00" end="00:01:23.86">If you do have a DeSales ID, the 14-digit barcode is on the back of your ID card,</p>
<p begin="00:01:23.86" end="00:01:25.85">and it&apos;s very easy to find there.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:25.85" end="00:01:30.57">We encourage you to take a look at our resources-they can really help you</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:30.57" end="00:01:33.48">with your projects in all of your courses.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:33.48" end="00:01:39.58">One of the services we&apos;re proudest of, we offer one-on-one appointments</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:39.58" end="00:01:44.37">with public services librarians to help you with your research project.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:44.37" end="00:01:49.83">We can do that if you come into the building, but we can we also do it over the phone</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:49.83" end="00:01:53.60">if you&apos;re never on campus, and we can do it electronically.</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:53.60" end="00:01:58.33">We&apos;ve found that the librarians like to do this, and it&apos;s very beneficial to you especially</p>
    
<p begin="00:01:58.33" end="00:02:02.25">to make an appointment at the beginning of a research project</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:02.25" end="00:02:06.34">because we can help you save time and we can point you in the right direction</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:06.34" end="00:02:08.38">for all the resources we have available.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:08.38" end="00:02:12.14">It can be a little overwhelming at first to take a look at our web page</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:12.14" end="00:02:15.61">and realize how much material is available to you there.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:15.61" end="00:02:20.13">We&apos;re ready, willing, and able to help you to get you started on that.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:20.13" end="00:02:23.89">And to contact us, our phone numbers are web page.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:23.89" end="00:02:27.40">You can call any of the public services librarians and we&apos;d be happy to work</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:27.40" end="00:02:29.84">with you to set p that appointment.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:29.84" end="00:02:33.91">And if you need something immediately, we can certainly help you over the phone,</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:33.91" end="00:02:37.16">or email as soon as you want to contact us.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:37.16" end="00:02:38.33">And we&apos;re always here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:38.33" end="00:02:42.98">Our hours are 8:30 to midnight during the week, and on Sundays.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:42.98" end="00:02:46.47">So you&apos;re welcome to come to the building if you are on campus</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:46.47" end="00:02:48.90">and we can help directly you there.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:48.90" end="00:02:54.17">Another important thing to look for on the library web page are online guides</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:54.17" end="00:02:58.21">to various subjects, and specifically, various majors.</p>
    
<p begin="00:02:58.21" end="00:03:02.15">If you&apos;re a business major, we have a specific guide that points you to the data bases</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:02.15" end="00:03:05.80">that would be helpful, as well as all kinds of other resources.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:05.80" end="00:03:12.29">The other thing we&apos;ve created within the last year is an online guide called Introduction</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:12.29" end="00:03:13.16">to Research.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:13.16" end="00:03:17.01">We found that beginning students really find this useful.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:17.01" end="00:03:23.40">If provides you information on how to get started on your paper, how to narrow your topic</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:23.40" end="00:03:29.61">or broaden your topic, and it also includes work on how to develop your thesis statement,</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:29.61" end="00:03:35.25">as well as a lot of help for creating those citations for your works cited pages.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:35.25" end="00:03:38.45">I encourage you to find that and take a look at it.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:38.45" end="00:03:43.89">Especially when you&apos;re writing your first paper, this can be a bit helpful for you.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:43.89" end="00:03:48.73">And, one of the very beginning databases you might want to try</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:48.73" end="00:03:51.93">on our database page is called Academic Search Premier.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:51.93" end="00:03:55.37">It&apos;s in the very beginning, it&apos;s at the top of the page.</p>
    
<p begin="00:03:55.37" end="00:04:00.70">It&apos;s very useful because it covers a broad range of disciplines, lots of different topics.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:00.70" end="00:04:05.76">So it&apos;s a really good place to start doing your research to get a little overview</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:05.76" end="00:04:07.90">of your topic and get you started.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:07.90" end="00:04:15.84">And it includes a great deal of full-text journal articles that you can get immediately.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:15.84" end="00:04:19.58">It also indexes titles which are not in full text.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:19.58" end="00:04:25.57">But, if we find something that&apos;s very good for your paper, and it&apos;s not available in full text,</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:25.57" end="00:04:28.89">we can get it for you through interlibrary loan.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:28.89" end="00:04:32.24">And that&apos;s another advantage of being a DeSales student.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:32.24" end="00:04:35.78">You can borrow books and other materials directly</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:35.78" end="00:04:38.83">from other institutions in the Lehigh Valley.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:38.83" end="00:04:46.25">That would include Lehigh, Cedar Crest, Moravian, Muhlenberg, as well as Lafayette.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:46.25" end="00:04:51.69">You can take your DeSales ID and borrow directly at those institutions.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:51.69" end="00:04:56.69">And we have interlibrary loan agreements with all of those, so we get the materials</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:56.69" end="00:04:58.87">from those institutions very fast.</p>
    
<p begin="00:04:58.87" end="00:05:01.55">We also can borrow from libraries across the country</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:01.55" end="00:05:04.73">for whom we have interlibrary loan agreements.</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:04.73" end="00:05:06.92">But you know, when you need those things from another place,</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:06.92" end="00:05:09.03">you have to leave a little bit of time.</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:09.03" end="00:05:14.01">The electronic journal articles, we can get pretty fast-we can get those in a couple days.</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:14.01" end="00:05:17.03">The books may take a little bit longer, a few more days.</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:17.03" end="00:05:21.95">So you really need to plan ahead with your assignments so you get the very best work,</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:21.95" end="00:05:27.36">and you give us time to help us find the materials that we don&apos;t have available here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:27.36" end="00:05:30.19">Thank you for taking a look at this video.</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:30.19" end="00:05:35.13">We hope to see you in the building when you&apos;re on campus and we strongly encourage you</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:35.13" end="00:05:38.91">to take a look at the library web page so you can access the wealth</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:38.91" end="00:05:41.65">of information that&apos;s available for you here.</p>
    
<p begin="00:05:41.65" end="00:05:44.13">I hope to meet you sometime in the building.</p>
   

</div>
  

</body>


</tt>
